[
    {
        "raw_text": "These ailments to attacking players leave Hurzeler with limited options going forward, and Ferdi Kadioglu filled in on the wing after Gomez went off.\nHowever, after a slow start to the season, Welbeck has rediscovered his scoring touch in front of goal in recent matches.\nFollowing an assist against Barnsley in the EFL Cup, the forward also scored a brace in the 3-1 win against Chelsea at Stamford Bridge late last month.\nWelbeck also linked up well with Rutter and Yankuba Minteh as they tested one of the league's stronger defensive units on Saturday.\nHurzeler will hope for more of the same from Welbeck, who hit a career-high 10 league goals last season, when Brighton visit his former club Manchester United next week.\nPrior to his goal, Woltemade's only attempt in the match came with the final touch of the first half as his header failed to trouble Verbruggen.\nThe Magpies struggled to create chances for their striker for much of this encounter, especially from open play, as cross after cross seemed to evade the reach of the forward.\nHowe clearly noted a lack of quality in the final third and responded by replacing Anthony Elanga and Joelinton with Jacob Murphy and Miley at the break, and the latter made the crucial impact with his assist.\nIt was not enough to salvage a point, and Woltemade cut a disappointed figure at the full-time whistle having failed to force in a second goal in a stoppage-time goalmouth scramble.\nThis was another positive display from the Germany international, though, as he often dropped deep to link the play and dragged defenders out of position.\nWoltemade's ability to influence proceedings and find the net will be key ahead of Newcastle's next three matches, all at home, against Benfica, Fulham and Tottenham Hotspur.\nHis first three Premier League goals had all come at St James' Park, and the Magpies must start to build momentum back on Tyneside.\nBrighton report | Newcastle report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Hurzeler",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ferdi Kadioglu",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Gomez",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Welbeck",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Barnsley",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "EFL Cup",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Chelsea",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Stamford Bridge",
                "FACILITY"
            ],
            [
                "Welbeck",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Rutter",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Yankuba Minteh",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Hurzeler",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Welbeck",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Manchester United",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Woltemade",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Magpies",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Howe",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Anthony Elanga",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Joelinton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Jacob Murphy",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Miley",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Woltemade",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Germany",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Woltemade",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Benfica",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Fulham",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Tottenham Hotspur",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "St James",
                "FACILITY"
            ],
            [
                "Park",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Magpies",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Tyneside",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "\nHowever, after a slow start to the season, Welbeck has rediscovered his scoring touch in front of goal in recent matches",
            "\nHurzeler will hope for more of the same from Welbeck, who hit a career-high 10 league goals last season, when Brighton visit his former club Manchester United next week",
            "\nPrior to his goal, Woltemade's only attempt in the match came with the final touch of the first half as his header failed to trouble Verbruggen",
            "\nIt was not enough to salvage a point, and Woltemade cut a disappointed figure at the full-time whistle having failed to force in a second goal in a stoppage-time goalmouth scramble",
            "\nHis first three Premier League goals had all come at St James' Park, and the Magpies must start to build momentum back on Tyneside"
        ],
        "summary": "Welbeck has rediscovered his scoring touch in recent matches. The striker scored a brace in the 3-1 win against Chelsea at Stamford Bridge. He also provided an assist against Barn. Ferdi Kadioglu filled in on the wing after Gomez went off. Woltemade's only attempt in the match came with the final touch of the first half as his header failed to find the net. Newcastle's next three matches are against Benfica, Fulham and Tottenham Hotspur."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "Fabian Hurzeler decided to leave Welbeck on the bench for their EFL Cup defeat against Arsenal on Wednesday, and that rest seemed to pay dividends for the 34-year-old.\nAlong with his opener in this match, the forward has also scored match-winning braces against Chelsea and Newcastle United, as well as a brilliant free-kick at Old Trafford in a 4-2 defeat to Manchester United last time out.\nWelbeck's constant occupation of Leeds' central defenders allowed more space for his team-mates, with Carlos Baleba and Ayari both going close to scoring before the opener.\nMinteh, Rutter and Gomez all took advantage of that extra space too, with Brighton's two-goal hero left in acres of room for both of his finishes that came in simple fashion.\nThere were also positives for Hurzeler at the other end of the pitch as his side kept their first clean sheet in the league this season.\nWith a trip to rivals Crystal Palace next up for the Seagulls before the November international break, Hurzeler will be desperate for his team to build on this win.\nA raucous Leeds away support may have been expecting this result, as their side failed to score at the Amex for an eighth straight game in all competitions.\nIt continued a familiar, and more worrying, pattern for Leeds, who were unable to back up their 2-1 victory over West Ham United last time out.\nLeeds have now followed up their last seven Premier League wins with a draw and six defeats since they last won consecutive games in the top flight, back in November 2022.\nThe grey skies above the Amex were in keeping with Leeds’ lack of brightness in attack, with Dominic Calvert-Lewin again short of service and isolated up top.\nNoah Okafor and Brenden Aaronson struggled to make an impact, while Calvert-Lewin sliced wide an optimistic second-half attempt with his only real opening.\nFarke did try to push his side up the pitch in the second period, only for Perri's defence to be left exposed and punished in another disappointing away performance.\nLeeds must find a way to deliver away from Elland Road if they are to battle up the table, and they will have the chance to do just that when they travel to Nottingham Forest for a huge clash next time out.\nBrighton report | Leeds report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Fabian",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Hurzeler",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Welbeck",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Chelsea",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle United",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Old Trafford",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Manchester United",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Welbeck",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Leeds",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Carlos Baleba",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ayari",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Minteh",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Rutter",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Gomez",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Hurzeler",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Crystal Palace",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Seagulls",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Hurzeler",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Amex",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Leeds",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "West Ham United",
                "LOCATION"
            ],
            [
                "Amex",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Leeds",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Dominic",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Noah",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Okafor",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Brenden Aaronson",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Farke",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Perri",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Elland",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Nottingham Forest",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "\nMinteh, Rutter and Gomez all took advantage of that extra space too, with Brighton's two-goal hero left in acres of room for both of his finishes that came in simple fashion"
        ],
        "summary": "Brighton and Hove Albion beat Leeds United 2-0 in the EFL Cup. Fabian Hurzeler's side kept their first clean sheet in the league this season. Leeds failed to score at the Amex for an eighth straight game in all competitions. Dominic Calvert-Lewin again short of service and isolated up top. Leeds travel to Nottingham Forest for a huge clash next time out. Crystal Palace are next up for the Seagulls at Selhurst Park on Saturday."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "Despite being swarmed by defenders, he impressed down the right and saw his name up in lights when Cole Palmer’s blocked cross deflected to him, only to launch his effort high over the bar.\nEstevao's fellow substitutes also added a new dimension, though neither Delap nor Santos could find the golden touch, leaving Maresca with problems to solve ahead of another London derby against West Ham United on Friday.\nHaving capped their superb 2024/25 campaign with their FA Cup victory, Palace started 2025/26 in a similar vein by winning the FA Community Shield.\nBut for all their joy on the pitch, off the pitch, they have been in the spotlight, with the likes of Eze, Guehi and Wharton all being linked with moves away from Selhurst Park.\nWhile some managers have opted to leave out players with their futures in doubt, Oliver Glasner backed his trio and almost got an early reward with Eze’s driven free-kick, only for Guehi's push on Moises Caicedo taking him too close to the Chelsea wall.\nEze continued to prove a threat, with a free-kick almost teeing up Maxence Lacroix, while Wharton split open the Blues’ midfield with a through ball into Mateta, though Sanchez kept things goalless.\nPalace were content to play the second half on the counter, with Eze often the orchestrator, though he fired his last shot straight at Sanchez.\nGlasner will be buoyed by that performance ahead of their first European campaign in the Conference League play-offs against Fredrikstad on Thursday, before facing Nottingham Forest in their next league match next Sunday.\nChelsea report | Crystal Palace report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Cole Palmer",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Estevao",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Santos",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Maresca",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "London",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "West Ham United",
                "LOCATION"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "FA",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Eze",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Guehi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Wharton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Selhurst Park",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Oliver Glasner",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Eze",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Guehi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Moises Caicedo",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Chelsea",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Eze",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Maxence Lacroix",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Wharton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Blues",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Mateta",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Sanchez",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Eze",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Sanchez",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Glasner",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "European",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Conference League",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Fredrikstad",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Nottingham Forest",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Chelsea",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "\nEze continued to prove a threat, with a free-kick almost teeing up Maxence Lacroix, while Wharton split open the Blues’ midfield with a through ball into Mateta, though Sanchez kept things goalless"
        ],
        "summary": "Eze, Guehi and Wharton have all been linked with moves away from Selhurst Park. Estevao came on as a second-half substitute for Maresca. Neither Delap nor Santos could find the golden touch for the hosts. Crystal Palace face Fredrikstad in the Conference League play-offs on Thursday. They then face Nottingham Forest in their next league match next week. Chelsea beat Crystal Palace 2-1 in the FA Community Shield."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "Mbeumo made it three goals in two games, and it might have been a hat-trick had Verbruggen not tipped a strike on to the post, but for all of their attacking prowess, United were almost undone at the back.\nHowever, Amorim will take plenty of solace from the fact that United did not capitulate, and the Red Devils will look to make it four wins on the spin when they visit Nottingham Forest next week.\nBrighton have already earned big scalps against Manchester City and Chelsea this season, and they were hunting for a fourth straight away win over United.\nBut Fabian Hurzeler’s team were short of their best defensively, with errors providing the hosts with openings. At the other end, Yankuba Minteh wasted chances, failing to make contact with a Welbeck cross before being pickpocketed by a backtracking Cunha when one-on-one with the goalkeeper.\nGeorginio Rutter had the opportunity to change the tide on the stroke of half-time, pulling away at the back post to meet Maxim De Cuyper’s cross, only to fluff his lines under little pressure.\nHurzeler’s triple change on the hour sparked some lift into Brighton, with Minteh seeing a teasing cross excellently tipped wide by Senne Lammens, but United’s defence initially stood firm against them until Welbeck’s sensational effort.\nFerdi Kadioglu’s long-range attempt was pushed away by Lammens prior to Kostoulas giving the travelling supporters real hope of a miraculous comeback, but it was not to be.\nBrighton are back in action against Arsenal in the EFL Cup in midweek, before they host Leeds United.\nMan Utd report | Brighton report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Mbeumo",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Verbruggen",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "United",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Amorim",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "United",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Red Devils",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Nottingham Forest",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Manchester City",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Chelsea",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "United",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Fabian Hurzeler",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Yankuba Minteh",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Georginio",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Rutter",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Maxim De Cuyper",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Hurzeler",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Minteh",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Senne Lammens",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "United",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Welbeck",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ferdi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Kadioglu",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Lammens",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Kostoulas",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GSP"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "EFL",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Leeds United",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Man",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Utd",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "Mbeumo made it three goals in two games, and it might have been a hat-trick had Verbruggen not tipped a strike on to the post, but for all of their attacking prowess, United were almost undone at the back",
            " At the other end, Yankuba Minteh wasted chances, failing to make contact with a Welbeck cross before being pickpocketed by a backtracking Cunha when one-on-one with the goalkeeper"
        ],
        "summary": "Brighton and Hove Albion were held to a goalless draw at Old Trafford. Danny Welbeck scored the only goal of the game in the second half. Mbeumo made it three goals in two games, and it might have been a hat-trick had Verbruggen not tipped a strike on to the post. United will look to make it four wins on the spin when they visit Nottingham Forest next week."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "Casemiro also flicked a header wide while, at the other end, Mateta spun to break in behind, only to drag his shot past the left post.\nYoro was then caught on the wrong side of Mateta again and clipped his heel inside the box. The Frenchman found the bottom-left corner from the spot, but it was ruled a double touch and a retake was ordered following a VAR review. However, he held his nerve to beat again, drilling into the opposite corner.\nBut United levelled nine minutes into the second half, with Zirkzee bringing down Bruno Fernandes' lofted free-kick before rifling beyond Henderson from a tight angle.\nUnited's turnaround was complete nine minutes later as Fernandes rolled another set-piece to Mount, who fired his shot through a weak Palace wall and in at the near post, and the hosts never truly threatened an equaliser.\nPalace approached this game off the back of a frustrating 2-1 defeat to Strasbourg in the UEFA Conference League, but they knew a victory would lift them, at least temporarily, into the top four of the Premier League.\nHowever, Oliver Glasner's side are yet to fully get into the swing of their Thursday-Sunday routine – all three of their Premier League defeats this season have come after midweek European games.\nPalace were comfortably the more dangerous team in an open first half. Their first big chance saw Mateta shoot into the side netting after barging down the left flank, while Adam Wharton volleyed straight at Lammens when left unmarked.\nWharton slipped a sublime pass into Mateta in the build-up to the penalty, which saw the striker become the Premier League's first beneficiary of an updated law adopted for 2025/26, with double touch spot-kicks now retaken if the original attempt is successful.\nBut Palace wilted after giving up their lead early in the second half, leaving supporters to question whether fatigue was a factor at the end of another busy week.\nIf Palace are to make good on their ambitions to qualify for Europe again, learning to manage that workload will be vital. They are in midweek action on the domestic front against struggling Burnley.\nA run of three straight Premier League victories in October landed Ruben Amorim led to renewed hope that his team had turned a corner.\nBut November had proven a more challenging month, with the Red Devils drawing with Nottingham Forest and Tottenham Hotspur then suffering a demoralising 1-0 defeat at home to Everton.\nIt looked like their downturn would continue as they ended an error-strewn first half behind. Yoro was twice caught out by the intelligent movement of Mateta, while Matthijs de Ligt was fortunate that Eddie Nketiah could not take advantage after his slip allowed the striker in.\nUnited were again without Matheus Cunha and Benjamin Sesko in attack, but Zirkzee and Mount grasped the opportunity to impress.\nZirkzee's goal was his first in the Premier League for 25 games, having netted twice against Everton on December 1, 2024. The Dutchman survived a nervy moment just after scoring, though, as Noussair Mazraoui's deflection ricocheted off him and almost flew into his own net.\nWhile Zirkzee was helped by some suspect positioning from Henderson for his strike, Mount's goal came when a glaring gap opened in Palace's wall, allowing the midfielder’s shot to soar through.\nAmorim will be delighted to see his team dig out a victory without two of their big-money signings, and Thursday's home game against West Ham United offers them a chance to build further momentum.\nCrystal Palace report | Man Utd report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Casemiro",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Mateta",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Yoro",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mateta",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Frenchman",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "VAR",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "United",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zirkzee",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Bruno Fernandes",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Henderson",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "United",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Fernandes",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mount",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Strasbourg",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UEFA Conference League",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Oliver Glasner",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "European",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Mateta",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Adam Wharton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Lammens",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Wharton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mateta",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "League",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Europe",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Burnley",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ruben Amorim",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "November",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Red",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Nottingham Forest",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Tottenham Hotspur",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Yoro",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mateta",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Matthijs",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ligt",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Eddie Nketiah",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "United",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Matheus Cunha",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Benjamin Sesko",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zirkzee",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mount",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zirkzee",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Dutchman",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Noussair Mazraoui",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zirkzee",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Henderson",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mount",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Amorim",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "West Ham United",
                "LOCATION"
            ],
            [
                "Crystal",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "\nZirkzee's goal was his first in the Premier League for 25 games, having netted twice against Everton on December 1, 2024",
            "\nWhile Zirkzee was helped by some suspect positioning from Henderson for his strike, Mount's goal came when a glaring gap opened in Palace's wall, allowing the midfielder’s shot to soar through"
        ],
        "summary": "Crystal Palace beat Strasbourg 2-1 in the UEFA Conference League on Tuesday night. The win lifts Palace into the top four of the Premier League. Ruben Amorim's side have won three of their last four Premier League games. All three of Arsenal's Premier League defeats this season have come after midweek European games. Manchester United drew with Nottingham Forest and Tottenham Hotspur. But they lost 1-0 at home to Everton in November. United were again without Matheus Cunha and Benjamin Sesko in attack."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "As Spurs committed more players forward, Bournemouth continued to pose the greater danger, with Marcus Tavernier sending a shot into the side netting.\nSpurs’ probing finally resulted in a clear chance deep in stoppage time, but Udogie could not direct his header on target.\nToothless Spurs see their run halted\nFrank’s Spurs had enjoyed a dream start to the season, following their opening day win over Burnley with an impressive 2-0 victory at Manchester City last weekend. That performance suggested they would be well-equipped to handle Bournemouth, whose high-tempo press can often mirror City’s.\nHowever, Frank’s hopes of becoming the first Spurs boss since Nuno Espirito Santo to win his opening three Premier League matches came to a shuddering halt as Bournemouth kept the hosts’ in-form attacking trio of Brennan Johnson, Richarlison and Mohammed Kudus quiet.\nFrank will be concerned about how easily the Cherries’ new-look backline contained his strike force, and how little Spurs created in attacking positions.\nWith James Maddison ruled out indefinitely, Spurs will be hoping new signing Xavi Simons can provide that much-needed creative spark, with the Netherlands international watching on from the stands following his move from RB Leipzig.\nHaving failed to beat Bournemouth last season, Spurs once again came unstuck, with Frank’s men unable to produce the same solutions that troubled City so effectively a week earlier.\nSpurs have two weeks to prepare for London derby with West Ham United, but before Monday’s transfer window deadline, Frank may want to see further reinforcements come in to provide additional attacking impetus.\nCherries stand firm after striking early again\nFollowing a midweek EFL Cup exit as they lost 2-0 at home to Brentford, the Cherries would have been eager to get back to winning ways and build some early-season momentum.\nThey scored in the fourth minute in their win over Wolves last week, and held on for a clean sheet and all three points, with their new-look defence showing their competency after shipping four at Anfield on the opening day, and it was a similar story here for Iraola.\nNot only did Bournemouth’s defence make short work of Spurs, neutralising Richarlison, Johnson, and Kudus, but they got in on the act offensively as Marcos Senesi assisted the game’s only goal.\nWith Bournemouth reportedly looking to further bolster their defensive ranks with the prospective acquisition of Alex Jimenez from AC Milan, Iraola will be aiming for his team to keep up their resiliency when they face Brighton & Hove Albion after the international break.\nSpurs report | Bournemouth report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Spurs",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Bournemouth",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Marcus Tavernier",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Udogie",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Toothless Spurs",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Frank",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Burnley",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Manchester City",
                "FACILITY"
            ],
            [
                "Bournemouth",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "City",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Frank",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Nuno Espirito Santo",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Bournemouth",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Brennan Johnson",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Richarlison",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mohammed Kudus",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Frank",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Cherries",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "James Maddison",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Xavi Simons",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Netherlands",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "RB Leipzig",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Bournemouth",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Frank",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "City",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "London",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "West Ham United",
                "LOCATION"
            ],
            [
                "Frank",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Cherries",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Wolves",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Anfield",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Iraola",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Bournemouth",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Richarlison",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Johnson",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Kudus",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Marcos Senesi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Bournemouth",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Alex Jimenez",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "AC Milan",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Iraola",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Hove Albion",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "\nNot only did Bournemouth’s defence make short work of Spurs, neutralising Richarlison, Johnson, and Kudus, but they got in on the act offensively as Marcos Senesi assisted the game’s only goal"
        ],
        "summary": "Bournemouth defeated Tottenham 1-0 in their Premier League clash. Spurs have enjoyed a dream start to the season, following their opening day win over Burnley with an impressive 2-0 victory at Manchester City last weekend. Bournemouth face Brighton & Hove Albion after the international break. The Cherries are looking to bolster their defensive ranks with the prospective acquisition of Alex Jimenez from AC Milan. Cherries have won just one of their Iraola scored in the fourth minute in their win over Wolves last week."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "Yet with Yoane Wissa and Bryan Mbeumo having left, and club-record signing Dango Ouattara on the bench, there was a lack of firepower when Brentford had the chance to put their foot on the gas.\nHowever, just as all seemed lost, Carvalho was in the right place at the right time to ensure there was a sting in the tail.\nAfter a difficult summer, Brentford can take solace in an unbeaten start at the Gtech Community Stadium, and they next host Aston Villa in the Carabao Cup, before another west London derby in the league – this time against Fulham – next weekend.\nPalmer had been on the field just five minutes and 12 seconds when he got on the end of Joao Pedro’s header, and that touch of class had certainly been missing for Chelsea in the first half.\nMaresca did not seem happy as he headed in for half-time, and the proof was in the pudding as he turned to his bench – debutant Facundo Buonanotte, Jorrel Hato and Wesley Fofana the players to make way.\nAt first, it did not seem as though those changes had the desired impact. Only a last-ditch Trevoh Chalobah challenge prevented Igor Thiago from getting through on goal, while Chelsea’s entire team soon switched off from a free-kick, though they got away with it.\nHowever, Palmer swung the momentum in his team’s favour, as world class talents tend to do. His goal was his first in open play in the Premier League since January, though he finished in typically cool fashion.\nNeto became increasingly effective down the right as the match wore on, and Caicedo’s moment of magic looked like it would be enough.\nHowever, Chelsea never looked safe at the back, and Brentford’s equaliser will serve as a reminder of what they must improve on, especially if they are to get positive results from their next two games, with trips to Bayern Munich and Manchester United coming up.\nBrentford report | Chelsea report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Yoane Wissa",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Bryan Mbeumo",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Dango Ouattara",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Carvalho",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Gtech",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Aston Villa",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Carabao Cup",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "London",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Fulham",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palmer",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Joao Pedro",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Chelsea",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Maresca",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Facundo Buonanotte",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Jorrel Hato",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Wesley Fofana",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Trevoh Chalobah",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Igor Thiago",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Chelsea",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palmer",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Neto",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Caicedo",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Chelsea",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Bayern Munich",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Manchester United",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            " Only a last-ditch Trevoh Chalobah challenge prevented Igor Thiago from getting through on goal, while Chelsea’s entire team soon switched off from a free-kick, though they got away with it",
            " His goal was his first in open play in the Premier League since January, though he finished in typically cool fashion"
        ],
        "summary": "Brentford are unbeaten after a difficult summer at the Gtech Community Stadium. The Bees next face Aston Villa in the Carabao Cup and Fulham in the Premier League. Neto's goal was enough to secure the win for the hosts. Chelsea never looked safe at the back, and Brentford’s equaliser will serve as a reminder of what they must improve on, especially if they are to get positive results from their next two games. CLICK HERE for all the latest Chelsea news."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": null,
        "entities": [],
        "events": [],
        "summary": ""
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "Ahead of kick-off, Sunderland head coach Regis Le Bris spoke highly of his side’s identity to earn points through defensive solidity, but it was their attacking intent that set the tone early on Saturday.\nIsidor’s disallowed goal stirred the Stadium of Light into life, and the optimism quickly paid off when Mukiele and Hume combined for the opener.\nMukiele started his run down the left, fed Hume centrally, and latched on to the perfectly weighted first-time return pass before slotting the ball into the net, with Johnstone only managing a faint touch on its way in.\nSunderland should have doubled their lead midway through the first half when Dan Ballard’s flick-on from a Mukiele throw found Hume, who should have done better with his close-range header.\nAfter the break, though, Wolves began to find their rhythm, forcing Le Bris’s men to lean on the very defensive resilience he had praised. And the hosts did just that, withstanding a spell of intense pressure courtesy of some standout proactive defending from Ballard and Omar Alderete.\nDespite the pressure, the hosts still carved out openings, with Isidor firing his early effort wide just past the hour mark before they got a slice of luck right at the end.\nLe Bris’s side will now prepare for a high-intensity trip to Stamford Bridge to face Chelsea, with the two teams level on points.\nWolves entered the October international break in need of a reset after back-to-back heartbreaks – having taken the lead against both Tottenham Hotspur and Brighton & Hove Albion, they failed to hold on for victory in draws.\nHowever, the break appears to have done little to change their fortunes. Unlike in previous outings, Vitor Pereira’s side did not strike first on Saturday, instead offering minimal resistance as Sunderland comfortably played their way through.\nTheir best moment of the first half came from Jhon Arias, whose deflected free-kick from a tight angle grazed the top of the net as Wolves failed to register a shot on target before the interval.\nPereira’s side responded strongly after the break, with Joao Gomes’ volley rolling wide after some positive build-up play. The Wolves midfielder followed that up with another off-target effort. For their part, Munetsi and Hugo Bueno continued to deliver dangerous crosses into the penalty area.\nDespite dominating possession across the second half, Pereira’s side had to wait until the 70th minute to register their first shot on target – one that ultimately did not count – as wasteful finishing continued to frustrate the Portuguese head coach.\nWolves will continue hoping for a change of fortunes as they next host another promoted side, Burnley, in what could be a pivotal clash at the bottom of the table.\nSunderland report | Wolves report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Sunderland",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Regis Le Bris",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Isidor",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Stadium",
                "FACILITY"
            ],
            [
                "Light",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Mukiele",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Hume",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mukiele",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Hume",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Johnstone",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Sunderland",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Dan Ballard",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mukiele",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Hume",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Wolves",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Le Bris",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ballard",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Omar Alderete",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Isidor",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Le",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Bris",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Stamford Bridge",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Chelsea",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Wolves",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Tottenham Hotspur",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Hove Albion",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Vitor Pereira",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Sunderland",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Jhon Arias",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Wolves",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Pereira",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Joao Gomes",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Wolves",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Munetsi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Hugo Bueno",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Pereira",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Portuguese",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Burnley",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Sunderland",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "\nIsidor’s disallowed goal stirred the Stadium of Light into life, and the optimism quickly paid off when Mukiele and Hume combined for the opener"
        ],
        "summary": "Sunderland beat Wolves 1-0 at the Stadium of Light. Mukiele and Hume combined for the opener in the first half. Wolves failed to register a shot on target before the half-time break. Jhon Arias' deflected free-kick from a tight angle grazed the top of the Joao Gomes' volley. Isidor Le Bris’s side will now prepare for a high-intensity trip to Stamford Bridge to face Wolves. Wolves next host Burnley in what could be a pivotal clash at the bottom of the table."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "United entered this game buoyed by a monthly awards double, with Amorim winning Barclays Manager of the Month for October and Mbeumo named EA SPORTS Player of the Month.\nOf the three high-profile attacking acquisitions made by United in the last transfer window, Mbeumo has been the standout, and he stole a march on Spurs' static defence to score his fifth Premier League goal of the season during the first half.\nBut when United's rearguard action crumbled in the second half, it was De Ligt, rather than any of their star attackers, that saved the day.\nDe Ligt's last-gasp leveller capped an eventful day for the Dutchman, who saw a back-pass roll under Lammens' foot and wide of the post early on before playing an unfortunate role in Spurs' first goal.\nThe equaliser will have been a particularly sweet moment for De Ligt, who was part of the Ajax team that lost a memorable UEFA Champions League semi-final to Spurs in 2019.\nAmorim will be delighted by the character shown by his team, who host Everton at Old Trafford on 24 November, following the international break.\nSpurs report | Man Utd report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "United",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Amorim",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Barclays Manager",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Month",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Mbeumo",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "EA",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Month",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "United",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Mbeumo",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "United",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "De Ligt",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "De",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ligt",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Dutchman",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Lammens",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "De Ligt",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ajax",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "UEFA",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Amorim",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Old Trafford",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Spurs",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "\nOf the three high-profile attacking acquisitions made by United in the last transfer window, Mbeumo has been the standout, and he stole a march on Spurs' static defence to score his fifth Premier League goal of the season during the first half",
            "\nDe Ligt's last-gasp leveller capped an eventful day for the Dutchman, who saw a back-pass roll under Lammens' foot and wide of the post early on before playing an unfortunate role in Spurs' first goal"
        ],
        "summary": "Mbeumo scored his fifth Premier League goal of the season during the first half. De Ligt was the man of the match in the 2-1 win over Manchester United. The 20-year-old was part of the Ajax team that lost a memorable UEFA Champions League semi-final to Spurs in 2019."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "Brighton looked to hit back immediately after Thiago’s penalty, and generated a high volume of chances, with Minteh and Welbeck both firing off target, along with Rutter and Wieffer going close.\nBaleba’s rashness in Brighton’s box proved costly, but Hurzeler – who became the youngest coach to manage 50 Premier League matches – will be delighted with the persistence his team showed after the interval.\nWelbeck’s run and finish were matched by an equally fantastic delivery from Minteh, and Hinshelwood’s strike sparked wild celebrations.\nThat elation seemed set to turn to frustration when penalty expert Thiago stepped up late on, but Verbruggen made himself the hero. Next up is a tricky trip to Nottingham Forest, who stunned Liverpool in one of Saturday’s other matches.\nBrentford have now failed to win in any of their five Premier League visits to Brighton, even if they looked on course for something of a smash and grab before Welbeck got in behind their defence with just under 20 minutes of normal time remaining.\nKeith Andrews, in fairness, will feel his team were worthy of their lead heading in at half-time. Thiago continued his fine form by netting his seventh goal from his last seven league appearances, and the Bees almost doubled their advantage soon after when Ouattara‘s blocked shot teed up Yehor Yarmoliuk, whose volley skewed inches past Verbruggen’s post.\nFor all their bright play in the first half, Andrews’ side faltered defensively after the break as Brighton applied sustained pressure to turn the game around.\nYet given his form from the penalty spot, Thiago will have been supremely confident of rescuing a point. Ultimately, there was perhaps too much of a casual nature to how Brentford’s striker went about this pressure spot-kick.\nBrentford, and Thiago, will aim to bounce back next weekend when they host struggling Burnley.\nBrighton report | Brentford report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Thiago",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Minteh",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Welbeck",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Rutter",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Wieffer",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Baleba",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GSP"
            ],
            [
                "Hurzeler",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Welbeck",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Minteh",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Hinshelwood",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Thiago",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Verbruggen",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Nottingham Forest",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Liverpool",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Welbeck",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Keith",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Andrews",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Thiago",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Bees",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Ouattara",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Yehor Yarmoliuk",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Verbruggen",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Andrews",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Thiago",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Thiago",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Burnley",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brighton",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            " Thiago continued his fine form by netting his seventh goal from his last seven league appearances, and the Bees almost doubled their advantage soon after when Ouattara‘s blocked shot teed up Yehor Yarmoliuk, whose volley skewed inches past Verbruggen’s post"
        ],
        "summary": "Thiago scored his seventh goal in his last seven league appearances. Brentford have now failed to win in any of their five Premier League visits to Brighton. The Bees looked on course for something of a smash and grab before Welbeck's late strike. Next up for Bayern is a trip to Nottingham Forest, who stunned Liverpool. Brighton boss Paul Hurzeler became the youngest coach at the Amex Stadium. Hinshelwood's strike sparked wild celebrations."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "Martin Zubimendi scored his first Premier League goals and the first ever brace of his top-flight club career in a dominant 3-0 win for Arsenal, as Ange Postecoglou's first game in charge of Nottingham Forest ended in defeat.\nZubimendi opened the scoring with a wonderful volley from the edge of the box in the 32nd minute, before Viktor Gyokeres was teed up by Eberechi Eze – who was making his first start for Arsenal – 47 seconds into the second half.\nChris Wood and Gyokeres struck the woodwork at either end, but Zubimendi made certain of the result with 11 minutes to play, heading in from Leandro Trossard's cross.\nBack to winning ways after their 1-0 defeat to Liverpool, Arsenal lead the table ahead of Saturday's other games, with nine points from four matches. Forest are five points back in 11th.\nHow the match unfolded\nArsenal dominated the first half, with a series of set-pieces causing Forest problems. The Gunners' first big chance came when a Martin Odegaard free-kick was nodded down to Mikel Merino, who was denied by the onrushing Matz Sels.\nAfter Odegaard limped off injured, Arsenal went ahead from another dead-ball. Wood only half-cleared Noni Madueke's corner, allowing Zubimendi to send a brilliant volley past Sels.\nForest's first shot did not arrive until Morgan Gibbs-White fired wide in first-half stoppage time, and they went 2-0 down almost immediately in the second half.\nEze stayed onside to beat Nicolo Savona and cross from the left, handing Gyokeres a simple finish.\nForest almost halved the arrears when Wood diverted Dan Ndoye's cross goalwards with his chest, only for the ball to hit the crossbar.\nGyokeres then rattled the near post with a ferocious effort at the other end, and Arsenal made the points safe when Zubimendi rose to meet an inviting delivery from substitute Trossard.\nArsenal new boys turn on the style\nArsenal needed a response after spending the international break stewing on a frustrating 1-0 defeat to title rivals Liverpool.\nBut having already lost Bukayo Saka and William Saliba to injury in the early weeks of 2025/26, they suffered a further blow when Odegaard was forced off after failing to recover from a heavy fall.\nHowever, Arsenal have invested heavily to bolster their attack, and their new boys led from the front.\nMadueke was electric on the right wing, tormenting makeshift left-back Morato early on and forcing Forest into some desperate defending with a series of inswinging corners, one of which resulted in Zubimendi's stunning first goal.\nOn the opposite flank, Eze was handed his first start after a brief cameo at Anfield, and he took advantage of some static Forest defending to assist Gyokeres, who drew level with Erling Haaland at the top of the early 2025/26 scoring charts with three goals.\nCristhian Mosquera also made his first start in the absence of Saliba and was a candidate for Player of the Match, making one brilliant goal-saving challenge on Callum Hudson-Odoi.\nWith their new players adapting quickly, Arsenal will hope to maintain their momentum in their opening UEFA Champions League fixture at Athletic Bilbao on Tuesday before hosting Manchester City next weekend in the league.\nPostecoglou left with plenty to ponder\nForest made headlines during the international break when Nuno departed, with a 3-0 defeat to West Ham United in Matchweek 3 proving to be his final game in charge.\nThough Postecoglou only had three days to prepare for this match, there was plenty of intrigue about how the UEFA Europa League winner would set Forest up.\nWith Ola Aina injured and loanee Oleksandr Zinchenko ineligible to face his parent club Arsenal, Postecoglou fielded Morato at left-back, and he struggled to contain Madueke.\nOne enterprising first-half dribble from Madueke would have resulted in a goal for Jurrien Timber if not for a heroic challenge from Murillo. However, the centre-back was hurt in that incident and had to be replaced shortly after Arsenal's first goal.\nHaving barely threatened, Forest might have been relieved to reach half-time 1-0 down, but the game was effectively beyond them when Savona was caught ball-watching for Arsenal's second goal less than a minute after the restart.\nForest enjoyed a few bright moments afterwards, with Wood going close and Deadline-Day addition Dilane Bakwa looking lively off the bench.\nPostecoglou will try to take the positives and get to work on the training ground, with an EFL Cup tie at Swansea City and a Premier League trip to Burnley to come next week.\nArsenal report | Nott'm Forest report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Martin",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zubimendi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Ange Postecoglou",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Nottingham Forest",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Zubimendi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Viktor Gyokeres",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Eberechi Eze",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Chris",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Wood",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Gyokeres",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zubimendi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Leandro Trossard",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Liverpool",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Forest",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Gunners",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Martin Odegaard",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mikel Merino",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Matz Sels",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Odegaard",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Wood",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Noni Madueke",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zubimendi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Sels",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Forest",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Morgan",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Eze",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Nicolo Savona",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Forest",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Wood",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Dan Ndoye",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Zubimendi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Trossard",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Liverpool",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Bukayo Saka",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "William Saliba",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Odegaard",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Madueke",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Morato",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Zubimendi",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Eze",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Anfield",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Gyokeres",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Erling Haaland",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Cristhian",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Mosquera",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Saliba",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Player",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Match",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Callum",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "UEFA",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Athletic Bilbao",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Manchester City",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Postecoglou",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Forest",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Nuno",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "West Ham United",
                "LOCATION"
            ],
            [
                "Postecoglou",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "UEFA Europa League",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Ola Aina",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Oleksandr Zinchenko",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Postecoglou",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Morato",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Madueke",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Madueke",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Jurrien Timber",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Murillo",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Forest",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Savona",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Forest",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Wood",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Dilane Bakwa",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Postecoglou",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Swansea City",
                "FACILITY"
            ],
            [
                "Burnley",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Arsenal",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Forest",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "Martin Zubimendi scored his first Premier League goals and the first ever brace of his top-flight club career in a dominant 3-0 win for Arsenal, as Ange Postecoglou's first game in charge of Nottingham Forest ended in defeat",
            "\nForest almost halved the arrears when Wood diverted Dan Ndoye's cross goalwards with his chest, only for the ball to hit the crossbar",
            "\nMadueke was electric on the right wing, tormenting makeshift left-back Morato early on and forcing Forest into some desperate defending with a series of inswinging corners, one of which resulted in Zubimendi's stunning first goal",
            "\nOn the opposite flank, Eze was handed his first start after a brief cameo at Anfield, and he took advantage of some static Forest defending to assist Gyokeres, who drew level with Erling Haaland at the top of the early 2025/26 scoring charts with three goals",
            "\nCristhian Mosquera also made his first start in the absence of Saliba and was a candidate for Player of the Match, making one brilliant goal-saving challenge on Callum Hudson-Odoi",
            "\nOne enterprising first-half dribble from Madueke would have resulted in a goal for Jurrien Timber if not for a heroic challenge from Murillo",
            " However, the centre-back was hurt in that incident and had to be replaced shortly after Arsenal's first goal",
            "\nHaving barely threatened, Forest might have been relieved to reach half-time 1-0 down, but the game was effectively beyond them when Savona was caught ball-watching for Arsenal's second goal less than a minute after the restart"
        ],
        "summary": "Martin Zubimendi scored his first Premier League goals and the first ever brace of his top-flight club career. The Frenchman opened the scoring with a wonderful volley from the edge of the box in the 32nd minute. Eberechi Eze made it 2-0 almost immediately to beat Nicolo Savona and cross from Chris Wood. Jurrien Timber made the points safe with a first-half goal. Viktor Gyokeres drew level with Erling Haaland at the top of the early 2025/26 scoring charts with three goals."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": null,
        "entities": [],
        "events": [],
        "summary": ""
    },
    {
        "raw_text": null,
        "entities": [],
        "events": [],
        "summary": ""
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "However, Gueye’s absence through suspension was keenly felt here, as Newcastle carved through Everton’s midfield time and time again.\nIt started in the opening 30 seconds, with Keane inexplicably stepping forward and getting turned by Woltemade, who released Anthony Elanga.\nThe winger’s shot was saved, but the resulting corner saw Everton concede their earliest goal in a home league game since 2014.\nEverton appeared to be building up a head of steam after that blow, but their midfield was then exposed again in the build-up to Newcastle’s second, with a counter-attack leading to a corner, from which the Toffees never cleared their lines.\nIroegbunam’s miserable day was capped off when he gifted Newcastle their third, and it was no surprise to see David Moyes take him off at the interval.\nNot that Everton’s defence fared much better after the break, with Pickford, Keane, Jake O’Brien and Tarkowski all performing below their best. Dewsbury-Hall’s exquisite touch and finish for the Toffees’ goal will have done little to cheer Moyes.\nWith AFC Bournemouth coming up on Tuesday, Moyes suddenly has to deal with some troubling questions about the robustness of his defence.\nThe pre-match talk around Newcastle was whether Nick Pope would keep his place in goal after making a big mistake against Marseille in the UEFA Champions League on Tuesday, though that decision was seemingly taken out of Howe’s hands, with the former Burnley goalkeeper sustaining an injury in training on Friday.\nAaron Ramsdale, then, got the nod, but he was a bystander as Newcastle ran riot to get up and running on the road this term.\nThiaw’s opener hinted that Newcastle had watched how Tottenham Hotspur scored two of their three goals at Hill Dickinson Stadium last month, with Everton’s defence caught cold from a corner planted into the six-yard box.\nMiley was the deliverer of that set-piece, and he later got his reward for trying his luck in front of goal. Hall also saw a deflected effort loop off the crossbar before Woltemade showed his class on the stroke of half-time.\nRamsdale did not have much work to do until he had to claw James Garner’s corner off the line in the 53rd minute, with Alcaraz then rattling the woodwork on the rebound.\nNewcastle put the game to bed through another towering Thiaw header, after Woltemade had a shot blocked on the line by Tarkowski.\nDan Burn led an excellent defensive display, though Newcastle were caught napping somewhat when Barry saw his goal disallowed and Dewsbury-Hall scored, but those rare moments of complacency can be forgiven in such a dominant display.\nLike Everton, Newcastle play again on Tuesday, going up against Tottenham Hotspur.\nEverton report | Newcastle report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Gueye",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Keane",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Woltemade",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Anthony Elanga",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Toffees",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Iroegbunam",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "David Moyes",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Pickford",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Keane",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Jake O",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Tarkowski",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Toffees",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Moyes",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "AFC Bournemouth",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Moyes",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Nick Pope",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Marseille",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "UEFA",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Howe",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Burnley",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Aaron Ramsdale",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Thiaw",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Tottenham Hotspur",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Hill Dickinson Stadium",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Miley",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Hall",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Woltemade",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Ramsdale",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "James Garner",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Alcaraz",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Thiaw",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Woltemade",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Tarkowski",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Dan",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Burn",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Barry",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Newcastle",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Tottenham Hotspur",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Everton",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "\nThe winger’s shot was saved, but the resulting corner saw Everton concede their earliest goal in a home league game since 2014",
            " Dewsbury-Hall’s exquisite touch and finish for the Toffees’ goal will have done little to cheer Moyes",
            "\nThe pre-match talk around Newcastle was whether Nick Pope would keep his place in goal after making a big mistake against Marseille in the UEFA Champions League on Tuesday, though that decision was seemingly taken out of Howe’s hands, with the former Burnley goalkeeper sustaining an injury in training on Friday",
            "\nThiaw’s opener hinted that Newcastle had watched how Tottenham Hotspur scored two of their three goals at Hill Dickinson Stadium last month, with Everton’s defence caught cold from a corner planted into the six-yard box",
            "\nMiley was the deliverer of that set-piece, and he later got his reward for trying his luck in front of goal",
            "\nDan Burn led an excellent defensive display, though Newcastle were caught napping somewhat when Barry saw his goal disallowed and Dewsbury-Hall scored, but those rare moments of complacency can be forgiven in such a dominant display"
        ],
        "summary": "Everton concede their earliest goal in a home league game since 2014. Everton's midfield was exposed again in the build-up to Newcastle's second. The Toffees never cleared their lines from a corner in the second half. David Moyes has to deal with some troubling questions about the robustness of his defence. Nick Pope suffered an injury in training on Friday. Ramsdale was a bystander as Newcastle ran riot to get up and running on the road this term. Newcastle face Tottenham Hotspur on Tuesday."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "He stayed alive in the box for the first goal, having initially been overlooked for a throughball, and took centre stage with a fine instinctive finish despite being slightly off-balance.\nAn immaculate assist for Wilson, which was inch-perfect, was met by an equally impressive touch that sent it curling into the bottom corner, giving a sprawling Kelleher no chance.\nFor the second home game in a row, Fulham then benefitted from an awkward own goal, and when Pinnock put through his own net, the job was effectively done for the hosts, who have now recorded three straight wins over Brentford.\nSilva’s side will aim to build on their momentum back at Craven Cottage against Cambridge United in the EFL Cup on Tuesday before an away game against Aston Villa in the league.\nBees lack buzz on the road\nBrentford’s struggles away from the Gtech Community Stadium continued, with the Bees now having lost all three Premier League away games this season.\nKeith Andrews’ side started well enough. Damsgaard, back in the team after illness, demonstrated brilliant awareness to cut out King’s attempted reverse pass, before slotting home his first league goal since last December.\nHowever, Brentford were then punished for their own lapse in concentration at the back, with Iwobi pouncing to equalise, while they were sliced open by his brilliant pass moments later.\nDespite their best efforts, there was no way back after Pinnock’s own goal, with Igor Thiago and Dango Ouattara unable to make their presence known in the final third.\nJordan Henderson, on his 500th league appearance of his career, struggled to instil a sense of control in Brentford’s midfield, and Andrews will have plenty to ponder on with no more away games before the international break.\nInstead, they will welcome the prospect of a home double-header before the international break, even if the two Manchester clubs provide the opposition.\nFulham report | Brentford report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Wilson",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Fulham",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Pinnock",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Silva",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Craven Cottage",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Cambridge United",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "EFL",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Aston Villa",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Gtech",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Stadium",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Bees",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Keith",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Andrews",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Damsgaard",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Iwobi",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Pinnock",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Igor Thiago",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Dango Ouattara",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Jordan",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Henderson",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Brentford",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Andrews",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Fulham",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "events": [
            "He stayed alive in the box for the first goal, having initially been overlooked for a throughball, and took centre stage with a fine instinctive finish despite being slightly off-balance",
            "\nFor the second home game in a row, Fulham then benefitted from an awkward own goal, and when Pinnock put through his own net, the job was effectively done for the hosts, who have now recorded three straight wins over Brentford",
            " Damsgaard, back in the team after illness, demonstrated brilliant awareness to cut out King’s attempted reverse pass, before slotting home his first league goal since last December",
            "\nDespite their best efforts, there was no way back after Pinnock’s own goal, with Igor Thiago and Dango Ouattara unable to make their presence known in the final third"
        ],
        "summary": "Brentford were held to a 1-1 draw at home to Arsenal in the Premier League on Saturday. Brentford have lost all three of their Premier League away games this season. Damsgaard scored his first league goal since December. The Danish international was back in the team after illness. Igor Thiago and Dango Ouattara unable to instil a sense of control in Brentford's midfield. The two sides will play each other again in the EFL Cup on Tuesday."
    },
    {
        "raw_text": "Although they struggled in the defensive third, Wolves' attack gave some reason for optimism that Edwards may hope to build upon and ease ever-growing pressure from the Molineux support.\nJorgen Stand Larsen constantly occupied the Palace back line, winning the free-kick from which Joao Gomes almost scored, while the Norway striker also linked up well with Tolu Arokodare.\nArias provided a bright spark after coming on as well, and should have done better with his chance in the 75th minute when he stumbled over himself while shooting.\nAnother defeat, however, leaves plenty to think about for Edwards before their next league outing against Midlands rivals Aston Villa.\nPalace failed to win four consecutive games in all competitions last month, but Oliver Glasner’s side have now bounced back to go unbeaten in their last five.\nTheir resilience was key to breaking down Wolves as the visitors continued to pile on the pressure following every missed opportunity.\nGlasner was left in disbelief when Mateta’s first-half strike went wide of the post, which came shortly after they saw a VAR check for a potential penalty for a foul on Ismaila Sarr end with a free-kick awarded.\nSarr went close to scoring himself early in the second half, but the Palace winger fired over the bar with a first-time shot from Pino’s low cross.\nGlasner showed trust in his bench too, replacing Mateta with Eddie Nketiah in the 60th minute while the match was still goalless.\nNketiah almost found the back of the net in the final minutes of regular time, but his shot flashed wide of the target, with the result sealed.\nGlasner will need to continue relying on his whole squad, with a trip to Strasbourg in the UEFA Conference League on Thursday preceding their next league match at home to Manchester United.\nWolves report | Crystal Palace report",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Wolves",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Edwards",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Molineux",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Jorgen",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Stand Larsen",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Joao Gomes",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Norway",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Tolu Arokodare",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Arias",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Midlands",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Aston Villa",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Oliver Glasner",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Glasner",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mateta",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "VAR",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Ismaila Sarr",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Sarr",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Palace",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Pino",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Glasner",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Mateta",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Eddie Nketiah",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Nketiah",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "Glasner",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Strasbourg",
                "GPE"
            ],
            [
                "UEFA Conference League",
                "ORGANIZATION"
            ],
            [
                "Manchester United",
                "PERSON"
